{
    "subject": "resource/John_Hennessy_Saul",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Hennessy_Saul",
    "human_readable": "John Hennessy Saul is primarily about John Hennessy Saul.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9588374495506287,
            "question": "Who is John Hennessy Saul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9465910792350769,
            "question": "Who are some notable people associated with John Hennessy Saul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9383950233459473,
            "question": "What is John Hennessy Saul known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8412562012672424,
            "question": "What are some of John Hennessy Saul's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7794240117073059,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges faced by John Hennessy Saul in his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7662100791931152,
            "question": "What impact has John Hennessy Saul had on his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7253939509391785,
            "question": "What are some key publications or works associated with John Hennessy Saul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.681315541267395,
            "question": "Where did John Hennessy Saul study or work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6676506400108337,
            "question": "Are there any awards or recognitions received by John Hennessy Saul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6604750752449036,
            "question": "What are John Hennessy Saul's future goals or aspirations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Hennessy Saul is primarily about John Hennessy Saul.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1311_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards or recognitions received by John Hennessy Saul?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1311_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did John Hennessy Saul study or work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1311_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key publications or works associated with John Hennessy Saul?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1311_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1311_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"John Hennessy Saul is primarily about John Hennessy Saul\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple individuals with the name \"John Hennessy Saul\" mentioned in the documents, including a horticulturist and landscape architect (John Hennessy Saul (1819-1897)), and another person who was successful in merging Home Savings Bank into American Security and Trust in 1919 (B.F. Saul, son of John Hennessy Saul). Therefore, the triple is incorrect as it does not specify which John Hennessy Saul the text is primarily about."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about John Hennessy Saul, including his career as an Irish-born American horticulturist and landscape architect, his work on the National Mall in Washington D.C., and details of his personal life such as his birth and death dates. Therefore, the statement that \"John Hennessy Saul is primarily about John Hennessy Saul\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It doesn't accurately represent the main topic of the context information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}